

SUPREAKSHYA SHRESTHA

WEB CONTENT WRITER / SPECIALIST

Creative Copy Writer offering background in preparing well-structured drafts, editing posts and conducting keyword research. Versatile Content Writer proficient in researching, writing and editing diverse content. Works with minimal input to produce engaging, authoritative and error-free work. Autonomous yet communicative with 5 -year history of superior performance in remote environments.

### **EXPERTISE**

Content Management

Superb Writer and Editor

**Content Strategy** 

**Creating Content** 

Social Content Planning

**Editorial Content Production** 

Content Marketing

**Editorial Decision Making** 

### WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

2020 - 2022

### **Content Writer / Editor**

Brainstorm Force (remote work)

- · Completed thorough research into assigned topics.
- Provided writing support in fast-paced environment for variety of public-facing materials.
- · Wrote and edited high-quality content and visually impactful programs under deadline pressure with exciting, captivating, and authentic approach.
- Utilized exceptional writing, editing, and proofreading skills to produce engaging and error-free content.
- Performed keyword research to optimize content for SEO.

# LANGUAGE

**English** 

Nepali

Hindi (basic)

## **Marketing Executive**

ExpressTech System (remote work)

- Developed technical and non-technical marketing presentations, public relations campaigns, articles, and newsletters.
- Developed and executed marketing programs and general business solutions resulting in increased company exposure, customer traffic and elevated sales numbers.
- · Worked with communications team to drive internal promotion of company programs, initiatives, guiding principles and mission.
- Consulted with product development teams to enhance products based on customer interest data.

# CONTACT

+9779840840362

2018 - 2020

supreakshya278@gmail.com

Kathmandu, Nepal, 44600

### **Web Content Writer**

AccessKeys Private Limited

- Researched to develop thorough understanding of unfamiliar topics, competitors, industries and processes to present fresh, new angles and ideas within written
- · Developed and edited informative, highly engaging, concise content for company websites and social media platforms customized for target audiences and company campaign objectives.
- Interspersed thematic, frequently-searched keywords to optimize articles for search engine results and performed additional SEO-related tasks to maximize traffic to
- · Created seasonally and regionally appropriate blog article content, collaborating with sales, marketing and analytics departments to identify business trends and extrapolate seasonally-relevant topics.

### **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2020 Global College of Management

High School Diploma (3.9/4 GPA)

2013 - 2015 Tribhuvan University

Bachelor in Information Technology (Marketing, Writing)